Guide to the Kenneth M. Reardon papers, 1971-2015.
Reardon, Kenneth M. papers
- Series IV. Major Projects
  - University of Illinois Urbana-Champaign: East St. Louis Project, 1990 - 1999
    - PRC Conference Talk - "Bridging the Gap Between Grassroots Organizations and Local Authorities in the Planning Process", October 1997 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - NTAC Press, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Press (oversized), 1993, Undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - East St. Louis Projects and Publications., 1992 - 1999, Undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence and Press, 1993 - 1994, Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Ken's Press (and correspondence), 1983 - 1998, Undated (Box 7, Folder 3-5)
    - "Neighborhood Improvement Plan for Emerson Park", 1991 (Box 7, Folder Vol. 1)
    - "The Winstanley/Industry Park Neighborhood Organization: Area Housing Revitalization Strategy", 1994 (Box 7, Folder Vol. 2)
    - Homeownership Information and Finance Initiative (HIFI), 1994 (Box 7, Folder Vol. 3)
    - ESLARP Documents, 2000, Undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
      Includes Speech by Kenneth M. Reardon "Participatory Action Research in East St. Louis: Planning as if People Mattered!"
    - Walter Thabit Interview, Summer 1998 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - UIUC: Garden Hills Neighborhood Improvement Initiative, Undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - UIUC: Douglass Park Plan, 1997, August 1997 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - UIUC: N. Champaign Press Coverage, 1995 - 1996, Undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
      Includes "V. Douglass Park: A View from the Community" which is a summary of the results from a resident perception survey.
    - AS [Alta Sita Neighbors] Summit, 1998 - 1999 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - ESL HUD COPC Conference Controversy, September 23 - 26, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      Includes conference material, and news release.
    - Dunham Fundraising Press, 1996 - 1998 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      Includes a short appeal letter "Highlighting the life of Miss Katherine Dunham" and how Kenneth Reardon as a part of the ESLARP (East St. Louis Action Research Project) have helped her, A donation slip for the Datherine Dunham Centers for the Arts and Humanities and information for events of Katherine Dunham.
    - UP374 Fall Orientation - Emerson Park Action Research Project, September 7, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Contracts, Correspondence, and Notes, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Community Partners, Undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Select Funding Proposals for East St. Louis Housing Authority. East St. Louis Environmental Action Project, Undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Emerson Park Neighborhood Improvement Plan (NIP) and Neighborhood Summit, March 6, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Janni Sorensen's PHD Dissertation titled "Challenges of Unequal Power Distribution in University- Community Partnerships, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - WIPNIP, 1992 (Box 7, Folder Vol. 4)
    - Gaber's Article on Mixed Methods, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Neil Pieces's Washington Post Articles - "University-Community Breakthrough in East St. Louis", "One Poor City's 'Awesome' Project" and "University-Neighborhood Partnership Makes Gains in East St. Louis", 1996 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Reardon's Testimony Before State Legislature, December 1, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - East St. Louis Community Action Network (ESLCAN) Fact Sheet, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Richard Suttle Memorial, February 18, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Cultural Revitalization Plan, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Chamber Racism Complaint, August 22, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Select Maps, 1990 - 2000, Undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
      Includes Original Map of the City of East St. Louis
    - Historical Background Materials, January 15, 1961, Undated. (Box 7, Folder 30)
      Includes notes and Original "Summary Master Plan/ East St. Louis"
    - Youth Build Launch, Meeting Minutes, October 21, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - ESLARP Photos, Undated. (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Farmers Market Implementation Proposals, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - ESLCAN Organizational Materials, October 16, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 34)
      Includes Bylaws and Minutes from meeting.
    - Farmers Market Brochure, Undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - ESLARP Housing Policy Act, June 20, 1998, Undated. (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - WIPNO Organization Development Proposals, March 4, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - ESLARP Interim Reports, 1995 - 1998 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      Includes Annual Report 1995-1996 and President's Project Briefing
    - Neighborhood Technical Assistance Center (NTAC) Press, 1996 - 1999 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      Includes NTAC Newsletter, Copy of ESLARP 1994-1995 Annual Report, correspondence and mission statement of NTAC.
    - Proposal to Connect Community to Higher Education, December 21, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - WIPNO Press (Illinois Avenue Playground), 1993 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Farmers Market Press, 1993 - 1994, Undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
      Includes "Expanding Business and Employment Opportunities Through the Creation of an East St. Louis Farmers' Market" Proposal, Vendor's agreement and announcement.
    - Planners Network Conference, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      Includes Press Release from Mayor, conference highlights and press.
    - Alta Sita Summit Material, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - ESLCAN Code Enforcement Report and Campaign, February 17, 1996, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      Includes "East St. Louis Sanitation Code Violation Report: An Inventory of Eight Neighborhoods in East St. Louis, IL", Hand Edited Code Enforcement Document
    - ESLARP Brochure, Undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - ESLARP Project Updates, January 6, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - UIUC: Appoint Press, September 6, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - ESLARP General Press, 1996 - 1999, Undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Farmers Market Advertising Plan, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Masters Thesis Project by Denise Chaffee titled "Housing Assistance Planning and Homeowner Education: The Case of the Edgemont Neighborhood, East St. Louis, Illinois", 1992 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Emerson Park Development Corporation Brochure, 1995, Undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
      Includes invitation to meeting, survey of goals, correspondence, notes and flyers.
    - Sustainable Neighborhood Initiative, May 25, 1999 - June 8, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Emerson Park Neighborhood Improvement Plan Cost Estimate, December 13, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Olivette Park Action Revitalization Plan, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Olivette Park Data Book, January 25, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Olivette Park Comprehensive Plan and Cultural District Proposal, April 1995 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - "East St. Louis Farmer's Market: Expanding Economic Opportunities While Providing Farm Fresh Produce at Affordable Prices", 1996 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Minority Summer Program in Architecture, Landscape Architecture and Urban Planning, Summer 1991 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Olivette Park Neighborhood Summit Program, February 10, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Farmers Market Proposal UIUC, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Katherine Dunham Strategic Plan UIUC, November 1996 - February 1998 (Box 8, Folder 25)
      Outlines a strategy to re-establish the center as a vital arts organization in east St. Louis by improving its organizational capacity and preserving its valuable cultural resources; this folder also includes two letters commemorating Katherine Dunhum during black history month in February 1998 as part of a fundraising campaign for the Center, and a program for the DunhamFest celebration event.
    - Planning Community Overview UIUC, 1998 - 1999 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Emerson Park Plans Summary UIUC, 1997, Undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Farmers Market, September 22, 1997, Undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
      Includes development budget, proposals, vendors agreement, designs and phases.
    - Metro East Lending Group Proposal, January 11, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 29)
      Includes "Winstanley/Industry Park Housing and Community Stabilization Program" and "Creating a Community Development Corporation in the Winstanley/Industry Park Neighborhood of East St. Louis, Illinois"
    - WIP Neighborhood Five-Year Neighborhood Demonstration Area Strategic Community Stabilization Plan, May 1993 (Box 16, Folder 15-16)
    - Farmers Market - Vendor Training Program, April 23, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - ESLARP- Background Information, Undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Cornell University
    - New Orleans Planning Initiative (NOPI)
      - Urban Land Institute. " A strategy for Rebuilding New Orleans, Louisiana November 12-18, 2005" and Bring New Orleans Back Fund information., December 10, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Survey Instruments - Neighborhood Questionnaire, Undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
      - Urban Land Institute. " A strategy for Rebuilding New Orleans, LA" PowerPoint, November 12 - 18, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 31)
      - Request for Qualifications for City-Wide Planning Teams. The Unified New Orleans Plan., Undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
      - Scope of Services, June 15, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 33)
        Includes the "Request for Qualifications" Questions and Answers.
      - Times - Picoyune Article - "Shrink Proof" and "City" by Jeff Horne, Undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
      - "Rebuilding After Hurricane Katrina". Acorn Planning Principles PowerPoint, July 2006 (Box 8, Folder 35)
      - New Orleans. "District Recovery Planning Guide", September 27, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 36)
      - Progress Report, Spring 2006 (Box 8, Folder 37)
        Includes press following Hurricane Katrina, report titled "Rebuilding the 9th Ward Neighborhood: New Orleans Planning Initiative Results"; "Building Conditions" Survey Block Sign in Sheet, Missing/Clean survey sheet and ACORN - University Partnership Progress Update
      - New Orleans Resource Guide, January 18, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 38)
      - New Orleans 9th Ward Recovery Plan, Undated (Box 8, Folder 39)
      - Completed Street Infrastructure and Condition Assessment Surveys, and map., October 2006 (Box 8, Folder 40)
      - New Orleans, January 2008 (Box 8, Folder 41)
        Correspondence, maps, notes, paper titled " Promoting Economic and Community Development in Challenged Regions Through Participatory Planning, Design and Development: A Collaborative Effort by Cornell University and the University of Catania"
      - The Unified New Orleans Plan (UNOP) - Community Support Organization (CSO) members announced, August 28, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - New Orleans Press, 1996 - 1998 (Box 8, Folder 43)
      - New Orleans Work Weekend, January 2006 (Box 8, Folder 44)
        Includes The New Orleans Planning Initiative January Service Trip documents
      - Acorn Contract, September 26, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 45)
        Includes Kenneth Reardon's notes from meeting.
      - Annual Update, Spring 2006 (Box 8, Folder 46)
        Includes "Rebuilding the Ninth Ward Neighborhood: New Orleans Planning Initiative Results"
      - New Orleans Planning Initiative brochure, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 47)
      - New Orleans Planning Initiative Brochure and Bulletin, 2010; CD-2481 (Box 8, Folder 47)
      - Cornell Institute for Public Policy (CIPA) Report, May 15, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 48)
        "Housing, Services & Viability: A Revitalization Model". Rebuilding the Ninth Ward, New Orleans following Hurricane Katrina
      - Viability Restoration Model, May 15, 2006; CD-2482 (Box 8, Folder 48)
      - Completed Condition Assessment Surveys, October 2006 (Box 9, Folder 1-3)
      - UNOP Deliverables, September - October 2006 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Newsletter - New Orleans Planning Initiative (NOPI), October 2005 - May 2006 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Fundraising, March 2006 - March 2007 (Box 9, Folder 6)
        New Orleans Presentation. Eagle Bridge Machine (EBM) and Tool contributes to Cornell for New Orleans.
      - September Field Trip, September 2006 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Field Work, October 25, 2006 - October 29, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 8)
        Includes a guide for interview residents about rebuilding the 9th Ward, cold calling script, completed surveys by community members and web surveys
      - October Field Trip - New Orleans, October 25, 2006 - October 29, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 9)
        Includes blank conditions assessment surveys and a guide"Our Work in Districts 7 & 8, New Orleans, LA. A guide to the students' place in the recovery planning process in New Orleans and the people and places that we will encounter."
      - CRP 330 CRP 530: Cleveland Field Trip, Fall 2006 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - UNOP, October 2006 (Box 9, Folder 11)
        Includes District Recovery Assessment and Planning Guide, suggested outline, deadlines and responsibilities and community outreach documents
      - Gap Analysis, 2000 - 2006, Undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
        Includes Documents for the New Orleans Planning Effort and ACORN Housing Planning Team members.
      - General Operating Proposal, May 2007 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - The New Orleans Planning Initiative/ ACORN Housing Summer Internship Program materials, correspondence and applications., 2006 - 2007 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - ACORN Housing/ University Partnership Team Management Matrix, September 2006 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - News Clippings, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 16)
      - Preliminary framework - People's Plan, Undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
        Includes basemaps (Planning District 7 New Orleans Base Map and Planning District 8 New Orleans Base Map) and list of contacts
      - People's Plan (Draft), January 6, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 18-19)
        Includes "A People's Plan for Overcoming the Hurricane Katrina Blues" ACORN Housing, ACORN Housing University partnership, Cornell University, Columbia University and University of Illinois at Urbana - Champaign
      - People's Plan Executive Summary, January 6, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 20)
      - Lower 9th Ward Plan, Cornell, January 6, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 21)
      - Physical Conditions, Undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
        Includes Housing Conditions Assessment Form and handwritten notes about the 9th Ward, charts and contact information
      - Plan Elements (Preliminary Draft), Undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
        Includes. "7th District Recovery Plan and "7th and 8th District Recovery Plan". ACORN Housing/University Partnership
      - Planning Meetings, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 24)
        Includes meeting notes with Pratt Institute, notes and ACORN Housing Planning Summit
      - Policy Proposals, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 25)
        Includes "Cornell City and Regional Planning Workshop: Re-building New Orleans 9th Ward"; "Smarter Storm Drains and Sewers Initiative", "New Orleans Case Studies"; "Expanding Housing Opportunities", "Municipal Service Proposals for a Successful Recovery of New Orleans' 9th Ward"
      - Press, 2006 - 2007, Undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
      - 9th Ward Press, 2006, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 27)
      - 9th Ward can be Rebuilt (NOLA), 2007 (Box 9, Folder 28)
      - Cornell: Jones Lab Dedication, December 2006 (Box 10, Folder 1)
        Includes materials for the dedication of a memorial statue to Barclay Jones
      - Cornell: CRP Promotion, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - CRP History, Undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Cornell University: 50 Years of City Planning at Cornell, December 13, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Hayes, Urban Development, Spring 2007 (Box 14, Folder 4)
        Includes CRP659.04 "Urban Development Finance in New Orleans" syllabus
      - New Orleans Planning Initiative, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 5)
        Includes "The Shifting Landscape of New Orleans", oral history by student "Lower 9th Ward, New Orleans Interview and Photography by Brian Rosa MRP Student"
      - Lower 9th Acorn Press, September 2006 - March 2007 (Box 14, Folder 6-7)
        Includes notes, strategies such as "A Peoples' Plan for Overcoming the Hurricane Katrina Blues, "City of New Orleans Parks Survey Assessment", 9th Ward Recovery Plan, student work, District Recovery Planning Guide, documentation and rehabilitation study, maps, proposals such as "Ninth Ward Community Design Center", class material, "7th and 8th District Recovery Plan"
      - New Orleans: Action Plan, January 11, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 8)
        Includes "Action Plan for New Orleans: The New American City"
      - Cornell University: Katrina Survivors' Continued 11/7/05 Louisiana State University, November 7, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Liberty Economic Action Project (LEAP)
      - Liberty Steering Committee Meetings/ Town and Village Resolutions/ EDC, LDC, 2001 - 2005, Undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
        Proposed Expense Budget for Liberty LDC.
      - Cornell: Rochester Outreach, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 5)
        Includes materials for Genesee Avenue retail corridor study, Genessee street business survey, and packet for community outreach weekend workshop and Cornell Newsletter with designs for Milstein Hall.
      - Lower Genesee Revitalization Plan - Rochester, Cornell, August 2003 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Lower Genesee Street Revitalization Strategy, August 2003 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Liberty Economic Development Report, March 2004, May 2005, Undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
        Liberty, NY. Includes The Liberty Community Development Corporation Bylaws, PowerPoint, "A Framework for Local Economic Development in Liberty, and press.
      - Draft Budget, August 8, 2003 - January 4, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Social History of Liberty, December 23, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Contract, September 2004 (Box 10, Folder 11)
        Includes "Promoting Sustainable Development in Liberty, New York", housing proposals and more within the contract.
      - Ithaca Tour, April 2004 (Box 10, Folder 12)
        Includes 2000 Census, Neighborhood Statistics Program and agenda of tour.
      - Financial Documents, 2003 - 2004 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Handwritten notes, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 14)
        Includes notes for Immigration meeting and more.
      - Planning Process, May 15, 2004, Undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
        Includes "Reflections on Liberty"
      - Liberty I & II, 2003 - 2005, Undated (Box 10, Folder 16a-16b)
        Includes documents from the Liberty Economic Action Plan planning process such as "Proposal to Develop a Comprehensive Liberty Economic Action Plan" and documents about Liberty Community Development Corporation.
      - Nichols Plan (Draft) Cornell, February 2005 (Box 10, Folder 17)
        Includes "Greater Nichols Comprehensive Planning Initiative"; "Preliminary Outline for the Greater Nichols Comprehensive Plan" and "The Greater Nichols 2020 Plan: Building a More Vibrant Community Through Cooperative Action"
      - Interviews, 1965, 2003, Undated (Box 10, Folder 34)
        Includes "Development Plan Part I: Survey & Analysis Report Liberty, NY"; "Development Plan Part II Village of Liberty, Sullivan County, NY"; "Proposed Zoning Ordinance, Village of Liberty, Sullivan County, NY"; completed surveys.
      - Info Sheets, 2005, Undated (Box 10, Folder 35)
        Includes Economic Data Analysis, and PowerPoint
      - Press, Fall 2003 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Projects (Youth at Risk) Stats, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Social History, Undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Demographic, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - CRP 330/ CRP 530's Liberty Expedition and Liberty Economic Action Plan - Student Orientation, September 2003 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Main Street Project, Undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
        Includes "Liberty, NY Development at a Crossroad"
      - Work plan, August 27, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Liberty Planning Projects, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 8a-8b)
        Includes analysis on housing, tourism, physical planning, Area identifiers, projects, surveys, "envision liberty" materials, Liberty Economic Action Project Application and documents, community meeting notes, Cornell City and Regional Planing student information, interview summaries
      - All Teams Meeting for the Liberty Economic Action Project, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Liberty Youth Center Board of Directors Annual Review, December 2002 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Liberty Background, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 11)
        Includes "Welcome to Liberty" magazine and Liberty Economic Action Project Flyers
      - Administrative, July - October 2003 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - Memos, April 2004 - May 2004, March 30, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - Overhead/Proposal, September 2003 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Travel Reimbursement Request, November 4, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - Proposal and Agreement, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 16)
        Includes "Proposal to Develop a Comprehensive Liberty Economic Action Plan" (June 30, 2003) and correspondence
      - Nichols Newsletters, June 2004 - August 2004 (Box 11, Folder 17)
        Includes "Greater Nichols Comprehensive Planning Project: Preliminary Outline of the Master Plan for the Village and the Town of Nichols".
      - Liberty II Proposal, April 2004 - July 2004, September 2005 (Box 14, Folder 10)
        Includes "Liberty Economic Action Project Year Two, Proposed Work Program", "Opportunities Uniting Liberty Youth and Business", "The Greater Nichols 2020 Plan: Building a More Vibrant Community Through Cooperative Action.
      - Rochester Neighbors Building Neighborhoods Material I & II, 2001, Undated (Box 14, Folder 11-12)
    - Northside, Ithaca
      - Northside Plan Outreach Materials, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 18)
        Includes outreach material for other events such as neighborhood summit and clean up.
      - Northside Ithaca Plan Press Packet and Presentation, September 2001 - April 2002 (Box 10, Folder 19)
        Includes "Turning the Corner: An Ithaca Neighborhood - based planning initiative/ Official Press Packet" and PowerPoint titled "Strengthening the Northside P&C Plaza. The Redevelopment of a Community Asset"
      - Northside Neighborhood Improvement Plan, December 2003 (Box 10, Folder 20)
        Includes Final Adopted Plan called "Turning the Corner, A Vision for the Northside Neighborhood, Ithaca, New York"
      - Northside, November 10, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 21)
        Includes "Northside 'Turning the Corner' Development Strategy. Making a Great Neighborhood - Even Better!"; press involving Cornell students and planning documents
      - Northside Imaging Activity, Undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
        Includes "Neighborhood Documentation Activity: Imaging/Imagining Your Neighborhood" surveys filled out by residents.
      - Northside Plan, December 2003 (Box 10, Folder 23)
      - Lower State Street Corridor Study (background and description), August 25, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 24)
      - Northside Press, September 2001 - October 2001 (Box 11, Folder 18)
        Includes Neighborhood Planning Initiative, "Southside begins planning initiative", "Northside Outlines Future" and committee information.
      - Planning Matters, Cornell Department Newsletter, May 2007 (Box 11, Folder 19)
      - Ithaca NBP (Neighborhood Based Planning), Undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
        Includes "Proposal for a Neighborhood Based Planning in Ithaca", "A plan for Participatory Neighborhood Planning: Learning from the experience of other communities" and "The Northside Neighborhood Planning Initiative: A Participatory Process"
    - Press
      Mainly for Cornell related projects but it includes some other previous work.
      - Rochester Improvement Plan Press, March, 23, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 25)
      - Liberty Press, January 2004 - May 2004 (Box 10, Folder 26)
      - Northside Ithaca Press, January 21, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 27)
      - Cornell Activities Press - Northside, 1999 - 2008 (Box 10, Folder 28)
      - Elmira Press - Northside, December 2002 - February 2003 (Box 10, Folder 29)
      - Ithaca Southside Press - Northside, December 2002 - August 2003 (Box 10, Folder 30)